<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Lifevox • india</title>
    <link href="https://lifevox.github.io/in/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://lifevox.github.io/in" />
    <updated>2024-03-28T20:37:34+05:30</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Shiva</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://lifevox.github.io/in</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Affiliate Disclosure</title>
        <author>
            <name>Shiva</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://lifevox.github.io/in/affiliate-disclosure/"/>
        <id>https://lifevox.github.io/in/affiliate-disclosure/</id>
        <media:content url="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/13/affiliate-disclosure.jpg" medium="image" />

        <updated>2024-03-28T20:11:21+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/13/affiliate-disclosure.jpg" alt="affiliate disclosure" />
                    Disclosure of Material Connection: Some of the links in this website are affiliate links. This means if you click on the link and purchase the item, the owner of this website will receive an affiliate commission. Regardless, the owner of this website only recommend products&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/13/affiliate-disclosure.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="affiliate disclosure" /></p>
                <p>Disclosure of Material Connection: Some of the links in this website are affiliate links. This means if you click on the link and purchase the item, the owner of this website will receive an affiliate commission. Regardless, the owner of this website only recommend products or services that will add value to the readers. The owner of this website is disclosing this in accordance with the Federal Trade Commission’s <a href="http://www.access.gpo.gov/nara/cfr/waisidx_03/16cfr255_03.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">16 CFR, Part 255</a>: Guides Concerning the Use of Endorsements and Testimonials in Advertising.</p>
<p>This website may accept forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.</p>
<p>The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this website. That content, advertising space or post may not always be identified as paid or sponsored content.</p>
<p>The owner(s) of this website may be compensated to provide opinions on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this website receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this website are purely the author. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.</p>
<p>This website does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>10 Simple Reasons To Remove Spyware From Your Computer</title>
        <author>
            <name>Shiva</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://lifevox.github.io/in/10-simple-reasons-to-remove-spyware-from-your-computer/"/>
        <id>https://lifevox.github.io/in/10-simple-reasons-to-remove-spyware-from-your-computer/</id>
        <media:content url="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/12/Malware.jpg" medium="image" />
            <category term="PC"/>
            <category term="Electronics"/>
            <category term="Computers"/>

        <updated>2024-03-04T18:53:20+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/12/Malware.jpg" alt="" />
                    Is your computer been running slower than regular? Are you involved someone may be able to get right of entry to your computer and steal your personal statistics and use it in opposition to you? If so, these are feelings I actually have shared with&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/12/Malware.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p>Is your computer been running slower than regular? Are you involved someone may be able to get right of entry to your computer and steal your personal statistics and use it in opposition to you? If so, these are feelings I actually have shared with you inside the beyond.</p>
<p>Some time back, my three-yr vintage pc was walking so gradual that I had to buy a new laptop. Or at the least I concept I wished a new laptop. Then inside a depend of weeks of browsing at the Internet, my new pc became also going for walks so slowly. In addition, a few packages did not run properly on my pc, and I did now not recognize a number of the packages that have been going for walks on my laptop. That scared me maximum. Were these applications that have been monitoring my keystrokes on my laptop or programs I just no longer do not forget installing? I knew I needed to find a answer and solution fast.</p>
<p>The truth is, we are able to all positioned up with a slow laptop, but only a few folks could want others to have get admission to to the facts on our computer systems, however that is precisely what can happen while spyware or malware is loaded on our computer systems with out our knowledge.</p>
<p>According to Spyware Nuker’s web website online, “Spyware packages are applications and documents that cover on your PC's difficult drive without your direct information. These applications allow hackers and advertising and marketing companies to tune your every move, both on-line or even when you work offline. They can tune the web sites you go to, the objects that you buy on-line, the emails you send and receive, your Instant Message dialog, and worst of all they can even document your credit score card range, private identification numbers, and all your passwords. If you use dial-up to hook up with the Internet then spyware can be used to invoice 900 numbers on your smartphone invoice. This is only a brief list of the harm that spyware can motive.”</p>
<p>The web web site additionally provides information that display adware is a large hassle effecting many humans. "27.3 million Americans were victims of identity theft in the closing five years, together with nine.91 million people or 4.6% of the populace inside the final year on my own."</p>
<p>In addition, it's far very easy in your computer to grow to be infected with spyware as "The majority of all downloadable video games, music, screensavers, and so forth., can infect your computer with SpyWare or AdWare. Most people do no longer understand that after virtually clicking on a random "pop up" advert, their computers may additionally have been infected with SpyWare or AdWare."</p>
<p>No count how we get spyware, here are 10 very actual reasons you don’t need adware on your laptop.</p>
<p>1. Your laptop may additionally start jogging slower<br>2. Some applications to your pc will not run effectively<br>three. You won't apprehend programs which are now for your pc due to the fact they will have been mounted there by using a spyware related internet website online or software you loaded on your pc.</p>
<p>In addition, you is probably worried that:</p>
<p>four. Someone is probably able to examine your e-mails<br>5. Someone is probably capable of get entry to your email list<br>6. Someone might be able to see you music the keystrokes you type<br>7. Someone might be able to access your credit score card facts on your laptop<br>eight. Someone is probably capable of get entry to your passwords list in your computer<br>9. Someone is probably capable of steal your social safety wide variety<br>10. Someone is probably able to tune all of the net websites you go to</p>
<p>As I mentioned, most of these programs get on your pc with out you even knowing, but any other frustrating component is I diagnosed some of those programs due to the fact I don't forget installing AND uninstalling them! So now I recognize that once we deploy a number of those available little utilities to tune passwords on-line or applications to help with email or hold music of the weather, even if we uninstall them, they'll now not be gone from our computer systems. They are nevertheless in our computers, ready to secret agent on us, at the least.</p>
<p>A awesome manner to locate and put off adware is to run a adware detector and remover. Most spyware detection and elimination software nowadays offers a unfastened experiment to affirm which you do or do now not have spyware in your computer.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Top 5 Laptops Under $1000 in 2024</title>
        <author>
            <name>Shiva</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://lifevox.github.io/in/top-5-laptops-under-dollar1000-in-2024/"/>
        <id>https://lifevox.github.io/in/top-5-laptops-under-dollar1000-in-2024/</id>
        <media:content url="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/11/Laptop.jpg" medium="image" />
            <category term="Laptops"/>
            <category term="Electronics"/>

        <updated>2024-03-28T20:35:58+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/11/Laptop.jpg" alt="laptop" />
                    Finding the perfect laptop can be tricky, especially when you're on a budget. But fear not, because there are plenty of excellent options available for under $1000 in 2024! Whether you're a student, professional, or casual user, this list has something for everyone: 1. Acer&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/11/Laptop.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="laptop" /></p>
                <p data-sourcepos="3:1-3:266">Finding the perfect laptop can be tricky, especially when you're on a budget. But fear not, because there are plenty of excellent options available for under $1000 in 2024! Whether you're a student, professional, or casual user, this list has something for everyone:</p>
<p data-sourcepos="5:1-5:230"><strong>1. Acer Swift Go 14:</strong> This lightweight and stylish Windows laptop offers excellent battery life, making it perfect for those on the go. It boasts a vibrant display and a comfortable keyboard, making it ideal for everyday tasks.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="7:1-7:204"><strong>2. Dell G15:</strong> For gamers, the Dell G15 packs a powerful punch without breaking the bank. It features a dedicated graphics card for smooth gameplay and a comfortable design for extended gaming sessions.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="9:1-9:289"><strong>3. Acer Chromebook Spin 714:</strong> Chromebooks are known for their affordability and security, and the Acer Chromebook Spin 714 is no exception. This convertible Chromebook offers a stunning touchscreen display and a long battery life, making it perfect for students and professionals alike.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="11:1-11:275"><strong>4. Apple MacBook Air (M1, 2020):</strong> While not the newest model, the 2020 MacBook Air with the M1 chip is still a fantastic option for those seeking a premium Apple experience at a more affordable price. It offers excellent performance, a sleek design, and long battery life.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="13:1-13:256"><strong>5. Lenovo ThinkPad X13s:</strong> If you prioritize battery life, the Lenovo ThinkPad X13s is a champion. This ultra-portable laptop boasts exceptional battery life and a durable design, making it perfect for professionals who need to stay productive on the go.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="15:1-15:312"><strong>Bonus Tip:</strong> Before you make your final decision, consider your specific needs and priorities. Do you need a powerful processor for gaming or video editing? Do you prioritize portability and battery life? Once you know what you need most, you can narrow down your options and choose the perfect laptop for you.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Top 5 Headphones Under $100: Budget-Friendly Audio Bliss</title>
        <author>
            <name>Shiva</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://lifevox.github.io/in/top-5-headphones-under-dollar100-budget-friendly-audio-bliss/"/>
        <id>https://lifevox.github.io/in/top-5-headphones-under-dollar100-budget-friendly-audio-bliss/</id>
        <media:content url="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/10/headphones.jpg" medium="image" />
            <category term="Headphones"/>
            <category term="Electronics"/>

        <updated>2024-03-28T20:30:11+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/10/headphones.jpg" alt="JBL headphones" />
                    Headphones are a personal choice, but finding a good pair within a tight budget can be tricky. Fear not, music lovers! This list explores some of the top options under $100, catering to different preferences and needs. 1. Soundcore Life Q35: Combining impressive noise cancellation&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/10/headphones.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="JBL headphones" /></p>
                <p data-sourcepos="3:1-3:218">Headphones are a personal choice, but finding a good pair within a tight budget can be tricky. Fear not, music lovers! This list explores some of the top options under $100, catering to different preferences and needs.</p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/10/soundcore-2.jpeg" alt="" width="450" height="483" sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/10/responsive/soundcore-2-xs.jpeg 300w ,https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/10/responsive/soundcore-2-sm.jpeg 480w ,https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/10/responsive/soundcore-2-md.jpeg 768w ,https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/10/responsive/soundcore-2-lg.jpeg 1024w ,https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/10/responsive/soundcore-2-xl.jpeg 1360w ,https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/10/responsive/soundcore-2-2xl.jpeg 1600w"></figure>
<p data-sourcepos="5:1-5:264"><strong>1. Soundcore Life Q35:</strong> Combining impressive noise cancellation (ANC) with a lengthy 52-hour battery life, the Life Q35 delivers powerful audio and long-lasting listening sessions. They even boast fast charging, perfect for those who forget to top up overnight.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="7:1-7:259"><strong>2. 1More SonoFlow:</strong> These wireless headphones stand out for their exceptional battery life, reaching nearly 57 hours with ANC activated. Additionally, they support high-resolution audio codecs, ensuring crystal-clear sound quality for discerning listeners.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="9:1-9:276"><strong>3. Audio-Technica ATH-M30x:</strong> This wired option prioritizes audio quality and comfort. Renowned for their sound clarity and detail, the M30x are a popular choice for studio monitoring and critical listening. Their comfortable design allows for extended wear without fatigue.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="11:1-11:218"><strong>4. JBL Tune 660NC:</strong> Offering a blend of affordability and functionality, the Tune 660NC feature decent ANC technology for the price. They're lightweight and comfortable, making them ideal for everyday use on the go.</p>
<p data-sourcepos="13:1-13:282"><strong>5. Sony WH-CH520:</strong> These wireless headphones prioritize affordability, offering a well-rounded listening experience without breaking the bank. They boast a comfortable design, long battery life, and Sony's signature sound quality, making them a solid choice for casual listeners.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Puravive</title>
        <author>
            <name>Shiva</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://lifevox.github.io/in/puravive/"/>
        <id>https://lifevox.github.io/in/puravive/</id>
        <media:content url="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/9/Puravive-Weight-Loss-10.png" medium="image" />
            <category term="Health"/>

        <updated>2024-03-04T18:34:09+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/9/Puravive-Weight-Loss-10.png" alt="" />
                    About Liv Pure Liv Pure is a dietary supplement that contains both liver purifying and live fat-burning complex made of selected natural ingredients. These ingredients are expected to rapidly detoxify your body as well as optimize liver function while giving you a toned body. According&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/9/Puravive-Weight-Loss-10.png" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <h2>About Liv Pure</h2>
<p>Liv Pure is a dietary supplement that contains both liver purifying and live fat-burning complex made of selected natural ingredients. These ingredients are expected to rapidly detoxify your body as well as optimize liver function while giving you a toned body.</p>
<p>According to the team behind the development of the supplement, the formula contains no stimulants, artificial additives, or any other sort of chemicals. It is manufactured in a GMP-certified facility approved by the FDA.</p>
<p>Every batch of Liv Pure weight loss supplement is tested for safety and purity. Therefore, it seems like the supplement is safe for regular consumption. Moreover, it comes in the form of easy-to-swallow capsules which also make the consumption convenient. Furthermore, the Liv Pure liver purification supplement is ideal for both men and women. So, you need not worry about that. </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Contact Us</title>
        <author>
            <name>Shiva</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://lifevox.github.io/in/contact-us/"/>
        <id>https://lifevox.github.io/in/contact-us/</id>
        <media:content url="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/8/Contact-us-2.jpg" medium="image" />

        <updated>2024-03-28T20:37:34+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/8/Contact-us-2.jpg" alt="contact us" />
                    If you have any questions or queries about this site or any of the produtcs we discuss on the LifeVox website then please feel free to reach out to us on this email (lifevoxofficial@outlook.com) Please allow up to 48 hours for a response. Please only&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/8/Contact-us-2.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="contact us" /></p>
                <p>If you have any questions or queries about this site or any of the produtcs we discuss on the LifeVox website then please feel free to reach out to us on this email (<a href="mailto:support.lifevox@gmail.com">lifevoxofficial@outlook.com</a>)</p>
<p>Please allow up to 48 hours for a response.</p>
<p>Please only ask questions in relation to this site or this sites content and the product I discuss.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>About Us</title>
        <author>
            <name>Shiva</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://lifevox.github.io/in/about-us/"/>
        <id>https://lifevox.github.io/in/about-us/</id>
        <media:content url="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/7/About.jpg" medium="image" />

        <updated>2024-03-28T20:16:55+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/7/About.jpg" alt="about us" />
                    Firstly, welcome to the About us page on the LifeVox website. On this page we will give you a quick breakdown on what this site is all about and the purpose for creating this site. So, on this site we review products that are getting a&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/7/About.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="about us" /></p>
                <p>Firstly, welcome to the About us page on the <strong>LifeVox </strong>website.</p>
<p>On this page we will give you a quick breakdown on what this site is all about and the purpose for creating this site.</p>
<p>So, on this site we review products that are getting a lot of attention throughout the internet, both on social media and Google.</p>
<p>we get the product and test it out, we also gather real true testimonials from other users.</p>
<p>Then we interview them or take our own thoughts and results to write a comprehensive review on the product giving you all the details, the good points, bad points and our thoughts on whether its worth buying or not.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Disclaimer</title>
        <author>
            <name>Shiva</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://lifevox.github.io/in/disclaimer/"/>
        <id>https://lifevox.github.io/in/disclaimer/</id>
        <media:content url="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/6/disclaimer-2.jpg" medium="image" />

        <updated>2024-03-28T20:10:37+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/6/disclaimer-2.jpg" alt="disclaimer" />
                    Your use of the site and the purchase of our product is subject to our Terms of Service, Privacy Policy. All content sold or provided by https://lifevox.github.io and its related companies are strictly for informational purposes only. While all attempts have been made to verify&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/6/disclaimer-2.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="disclaimer" /></p>
                <p>Your use of the site and the purchase of our product is subject to our Terms of Service, Privacy Policy.</p>
<p>All content sold or provided by https://lifevox.github.io and its related companies are strictly for informational purposes only. While all attempts have been made to verify the accuracy of information provided on our website and within the publications, neither the authors nor the publishers are responsible for assuming liability for possible inaccuracies.</p>
<p>The authors and publishers disclaim any responsibility for the inaccuracy of the content, including but not limited to errors or omissions. Loss of property, injury to self or others, and even death could occur as a direct or indirect consequence of the use and application of any content found herein.</p>
<p>Individual results may vary, which is quite normal for anything. The FDA hasn’t evaluated the statements provided on this page. Finally, make sure you consult with a licensed doctor before taking any supplements or making any changes to your diet or exercise plan.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>FTC Disclosure: While we are never paid to write a review, if you do click on a link from our site and make a purchase, we may get a paid commission.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Terms &amp; Conditions</title>
        <author>
            <name>Shiva</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://lifevox.github.io/in/terms-and-conditions/"/>
        <id>https://lifevox.github.io/in/terms-and-conditions/</id>
        <media:content url="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/5/Terms-and-Conditions.jpg" medium="image" />

        <updated>2024-03-28T19:55:18+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/5/Terms-and-Conditions.jpg" alt="terms and conditions" />
                    Welcome to LifeVox! These terms and conditions outline the rules and regulations for the use of LifeVox’s Website, located at https://lifevox.github.io. By accessing this website we assume you accept these terms and conditions. Do not continue to use LifeVox if you do not agree to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/5/Terms-and-Conditions.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="terms and conditions" /></p>
                <p>Welcome to LifeVox!</p>
<p>These terms and conditions outline the rules and regulations for the use of LifeVox’s Website, located at https://lifevox.github.io.</p>
<p>By accessing this website we assume you accept these terms and conditions. Do not continue to use LifeVox if you do not agree to take all of the terms and conditions stated on this page.</p>
<p>The following terminology applies to these Terms and Conditions, Privacy Statement and Disclaimer Notice and all Agreements: ‘Client’, ‘You’ and ‘Your’ refers to you, the person log on this website and compliant to the Company’s terms and conditions. ‘The Company’, ‘Ourselves’, ‘We’, ‘Our’ and ‘Us’, refers to our Company. ‘Party’, ‘Parties’, or ‘Us’, refers to both the Client and ourselves. All terms refer to the offer, acceptance and consideration of payment necessary to undertake the process of our assistance to the Client in the most appropriate manner for the express purpose of meeting the Client’s needs in respect of provision of the Company’s stated services, in accordance with and subject to, prevailing law of Netherlands. Any use of the above terminology or other words in the singular, plural, capitalization and/or he/she or they, are taken as interchangeable and therefore as referring to same.</p>
<h3><strong>Cookies</strong></h3>
<p>We employ the use of cookies. By accessing LifeVox, you agreed to use cookies in agreement with the LifeVox’s Privacy Policy.</p>
<p>Most interactive websites use cookies to let us retrieve the user’s details for each visit. Cookies are used by our website to enable the functionality of certain areas to make it easier for people visiting our website. Some of our affiliate/advertising partners may also use cookies.</p>
<h3><strong>License</strong></h3>
<p>Unless otherwise stated, LifeVox and/or its licensors own the intellectual property rights for all material on LifeVox. All intellectual property rights are reserved. You may access this from LifeVox for your own personal use subjected to restrictions set in these terms and conditions.</p>
<p>You must not:</p>
<ul>
<li>Republish material from LifeVox</li>
<li>Sell, rent or sub-license material from LifeVox</li>
<li>Reproduce, duplicate or copy material from LifeVox</li>
<li>Redistribute content from LifeVox</li>
</ul>
<p>This Agreement shall begin on the date hereof.</p>
<p>Parts of this website offer an opportunity for users to post and exchange opinions and information in certain areas of the website. LifeVox does not filter, edit, publish or review Comments prior to their presence on the website. Comments do not reflect the views and opinions of LifeVox,its agents and/or affiliates. Comments reflect the views and opinions of the person who post their views and opinions. To the extent permitted by applicable laws, LifeVox shall not be liable for the Comments or for any liability, damages or expenses caused and/or suffered as a result of any use of and/or posting of and/or appearance of the Comments on this website.</p>
<p>LifeVox reserves the right to monitor all Comments and to remove any Comments which can be considered inappropriate, offensive or causes breach of these Terms and Conditions.</p>
<p>You warrant and represent that:</p>
<ul>
<li>You are entitled to post the Comments on our website and have all necessary licenses and consents to do so;</li>
<li>The Comments do not invade any intellectual property right, including without limitation copyright, patent or trademark of any third party;</li>
<li>The Comments do not contain any defamatory, libelous, offensive, indecent or otherwise unlawful material which is an invasion of privacy</li>
<li>The Comments will not be used to solicit or promote business or custom or present commercial activities or unlawful activity.</li>
</ul>
<p>You hereby grant LifeVox a non-exclusive license to use, reproduce, edit and authorize others to use, reproduce and edit any of your Comments in any and all forms, formats or media.</p>
<h3><strong>Hyperlinking to our Content</strong></h3>
<p>The following organizations may link to our Website without prior written approval:</p>
<ul>
<li>Government agencies;</li>
<li>Search engines;</li>
<li>News organizations;</li>
<li>Online directory distributors may link to our Website in the same manner as they hyperlink to the Websites of other listed businesses; and</li>
<li>System wide Accredited Businesses except soliciting non-profit organizations, charity shopping malls, and charity fundraising groups which may not hyperlink to our Web site.</li>
</ul>
<p>These organizations may link to our home page, to publications or to other Website information so long as the link: (a) is not in any way deceptive; (b) does not falsely imply sponsorship, endorsement or approval of the linking party and its products and/or services; and (c) fits within the context of the linking party’s site.</p>
<p>We may consider and approve other link requests from the following types of organizations:</p>
<ul>
<li>commonly-known consumer and/or business information sources;</li>
<li>dot.com community sites;</li>
<li>associations or other groups representing charities;</li>
<li>online directory distributors;</li>
<li>internet portals;</li>
<li>accounting, law and consulting firms; and</li>
<li>educational institutions and trade associations.</li>
</ul>
<p>We will approve link requests from these organizations if we decide that: (a) the link would not make us look unfavorably to ourselves or to our accredited businesses; (b) the organization does not have any negative records with us; (c) the benefit to us from the visibility of the hyperlink compensates the absence of LifeVox; and (d) the link is in the context of general resource information.</p>
<p>These organizations may link to our home page so long as the link: (a) is not in any way deceptive; (b) does not falsely imply sponsorship, endorsement or approval of the linking party and its products or services; and (c) fits within the context of the linking party’s site.</p>
<p>If you are one of the organizations listed in paragraph 2 above and are interested in linking to our website, you must inform us by sending an e-mail to LifeVox. Please include your name, your organization name, contact information as well as the URL of your site, a list of any URLs from which you intend to link to our Website, and a list of the URLs on our site to which you would like to link. Wait 2-3 weeks for a response.</p>
<p>Approved organizations may hyperlink to our Website as follows:</p>
<ul>
<li>By use of our corporate name; or</li>
<li>By use of the uniform resource locator being linked to; or</li>
<li>By use of any other description of our Website being linked to that makes sense within the context and format of content on the linking party’s site.</li>
</ul>
<p>No use of LifeVox’s logo or other artwork will be allowed for linking absent a trademark license agreement.</p>
<h3><strong>iFrames</strong></h3>
<p>Without prior approval and written permission, you may not create frames around our Webpages that alter in any way the visual presentation or appearance of our Website.</p>
<h3><strong>Content Liability</strong></h3>
<p>We shall not be hold responsible for any content that appears on your Website. You agree to protect and defend us against all claims that is rising on your Website. No link(s) should appear on any Website that may be interpreted as libelous, obscene or criminal, or which infringes, otherwise violates, or advocates the infringement or other violation of, any third party rights.</p>
<h3><strong>Your Privacy</strong></h3>
<p>Please read Privacy Policy</p>
<h3><strong>Reservation of Rights</strong></h3>
<p>We reserve the right to request that you remove all links or any particular link to our Website. You approve to immediately remove all links to our Website upon request. We also reserve the right to amen these terms and conditions and it’s linking policy at any time. By continuously linking to our Website, you agree to be bound to and follow these linking terms and conditions.</p>
<h3><strong>Removal of links from our website</strong></h3>
<p>If you find any link on our Website that is offensive for any reason, you are free to contact and inform us any moment. We will consider requests to remove links but we are not obligated to or so or to respond to you directly.</p>
<p>We do not ensure that the information on this website is correct, we do not warrant its completeness or accuracy; nor do we promise to ensure that the website remains available or that the material on the website is kept up to date.</p>
<h3><strong>Disclaimer</strong></h3>
<p>To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, we exclude all representations, warranties and conditions relating to our website and the use of this website. Nothing in this disclaimer will:</p>
<ul>
<li>limit or exclude our or your liability for death or personal injury;</li>
<li>limit or exclude our or your liability for fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation;</li>
<li>limit any of our or your liabilities in any way that is not permitted under applicable law; or</li>
<li>exclude any of our or your liabilities that may not be excluded under applicable law.</li>
</ul>
<p>The limitations and prohibitions of liability set in this Section and elsewhere in this disclaimer: (a) are subject to the preceding paragraph; and (b) govern all liabilities arising under the disclaimer, including liabilities arising in contract, in tort and for breach of statutory duty.</p>
<p>As long as the website and the information and services on the website are provided free of charge, we will not be liable for any loss or damage of any nature.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Privacy Policy</title>
        <author>
            <name>Shiva</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://lifevox.github.io/in/privacy-policy/"/>
        <id>https://lifevox.github.io/in/privacy-policy/</id>
        <media:content url="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/4/Privacy.jpg" medium="image" />

        <updated>2024-03-28T20:00:38+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/4/Privacy.jpg" alt="privacy policy" />
                    At LifeVox, accessible from https://lifevox.github.io, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by LifeVox and how we use it. If you have additional questions or require more information&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://lifevox.github.io/in/media/posts/4/Privacy.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="privacy policy" /></p>
                <p>At LifeVox, accessible from https://lifevox.github.io, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by LifeVox and how we use it.</p>
<p>If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.</p>
<p>This Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in LifeVox. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.</p>
<h2>Consent</h2>
<p>By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.</p>
<h2>Information we collect</h2>
<p>The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.</p>
<p>If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.</p>
<p>When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, company name, address, email address, and telephone number.</p>
<h2>How we use your information</h2>
<p>We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:</p>
<ul>
<li>Provide, operate, and maintain our website</li>
<li>Improve, personalize, and expand our website</li>
<li>Understand and analyze how you use our website</li>
<li>Develop new products, services, features, and functionality</li>
<li>Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the website, and for marketing and promotional purposes</li>
<li>Send you emails</li>
<li>Find and prevent fraud</li>
</ul>
<h2>Log Files</h2>
<p>LifeVox follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting service analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.</p>
<h2>Cookies and Web Beacons</h2>
<p>Like any other website, LifeVox uses ‘cookies’. These cookies are used to store information including visitors’ preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the users’ experience by customizing our web page content based on visitors’ browser type and/or other information.</p>
<h2>Google DoubleClick DART Cookie</h2>
<p>Google is one of a third-party vendor on our site. It also uses cookies, known as DART cookies, to serve ads to our site visitors based upon their visit to www.website.com and other sites on the internet. However, visitors may choose to decline the use of DART cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network Privacy Policy at the following URL – <a href="https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads">https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads</a></p>
<h2>Our Advertising Partners</h2>
<p>Some of advertisers on our site may use cookies and web beacons. Our advertising partners are listed below. Each of our advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their policies on user data. For easier access, we hyperlinked to their Privacy Policies below.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Google</p>
<p><a href="https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads">https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads</a></p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2>Advertising Partners Privacy Policies</h2>
<p>You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of LifeVox.</p>
<p>Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on LifeVox, which are sent directly to users’ browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.</p>
<p>Note that LifeVox has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.</p>
<h2>Third Party Privacy Policies</h2>
<p>LifeVox’s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options.</p>
<p>You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.</p>
<h2>CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)</h2>
<p>Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:</p>
<p>Request that a business that collects a consumer’s personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.</p>
<p>Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.</p>
<p>Request that a business that sells a consumer’s personal data, not sell the consumer’s personal data.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>GDPR Data Protection Rights</h2>
<p>We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:</p>
<p>The right to access – You have the right to request copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.</p>
<p>The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.</p>
<p>The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>Children’s Information</h2>
<p>Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.</p>
<p>LifeVox does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
